const STORE = [
  
    {
        question: 'What is a f/stop?',
        answer: [
                'a function that controls the exposure',
                'the size of a lens',
                'how long the shutter is open',
                'the aperture size'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'the aperture size',
    },
    {
        question: 'Who makes the 5D model?',
        answer: [
                'Nikon',
                'Canon',
                'Sony',
                'Pentax'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Canon',
    },
    {
        question: 'What setting controls motion?',
        answer: [
                'the aperture',
                'the shutter',
                'ISO',
                'none of the above'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'the shutter',
    },
    {
        question: 'How do you control Depth of Field?',
        answer: [
                'the shutter',
                'ISO',
                'the aperture',
                'none of the above'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'the aperture',
    },
    {
        question: 'Who coined the term the Decisive Moment?',
        answer: [
                'Richard Avedon',
                'Irving Penn',
                'Annie Leibovitz',
                'Henri Cartier Bresson'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Henri Cartier Bresson',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is a pinhole camera?',
        answer: [
                'a light tight box with a pinhole punctured on one side',
                'a spy camera',
                'a surveillance camera',
                'a childâ€™s camera'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'a light tight box with a pinhole punctured on one side',
    },
    {
        question: 'Define the term flash duration.',
        answer: [
                'the power of a flash',
                'the time it takes a flash to recharge',
                'life span of a flash-bulb',
                'the amount of time light from a flash is present'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'the amount of time light from a flash is present',
    },
    {
        question: 'Why is a UV filter important?',
        answer: [
                'it protects the outer lens element',
                'to block unwanted light rays',
                'to enhance UV light rays',
                'all of the above'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'it protects the outer lens element',
    },
    {
        question: 'If you want to take a photo of the night sky, which piece of equipment it most valuable?',
        answer: [
                'a flashlight',
                'a long lens',
                'a tripod',
                'a polarizer'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'a tripod',
    },
    {
        question: 'What does the term ISO refer to?',
        answer: [
                'Internal State Optimizer',
                'International Organization of Standardization',
                'Isolation of Still Objects',
                'Immediate State Optics'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'International Organization of Standardization',
    }
];